{
    "subject": "resource/MySQL_Workbench",
    "predicate": "ontology/programmingLanguage",
    "object": "resource/C++",
    "human_readable": "MySQL Workbench is written in C++.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.829439103603363,
            "question": "What programming language is MySQL Workbench written in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7788742184638977,
            "question": "Are there any performance considerations when choosing C++ for a project like MySQL Workbench?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5406873226165771,
            "question": "Is MySQL Workbench a database management tool?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49244311451911926,
            "question": "What tasks can MySQL Workbench help you perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43389979004859924,
            "question": "What are some popular alternatives to MySQL Workbench?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22272321581840515,
            "question": "Can you list some software development tools written in C++?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18981295824050903,
            "question": "What are the potential challenges of maintaining software written in C++?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09866737574338913,
            "question": "Is C++ a commonly used language for creating GUI applications?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07541016489267349,
            "question": "What are the advantages of using C++ for software development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04353350028395653,
            "question": "Can you name other database systems that have their own dedicated tools?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=MySQL Workbench is written in C++.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8284_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the advantages of using C++ for software development?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8284_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is C++ a commonly used language for creating GUI applications?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8284_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the potential challenges of maintaining software written in C++?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8284_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8284_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8284_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8284_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8284_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8284_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8284_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8284_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8284_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8284_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8284_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention that \"MySQL Workbench is an application written mostly in C++\" and also mention that while there are platform-specific parts written in other languages, the core of MySQL Workbench is developed using C++."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"MySQL Workbench is an application written mostly in C++.\" This supports the statement that \"MySQL Workbench is written in C++.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}